Life is about the choices we make.
A Kiss Before Christmas is a tv movie, romance,
comedy film directed by Jeff Beesley.
Ethan, always the nice guy, wakes up in a new reality at Christmas.
Initially, he is enthralled with his new life but soon
realizes that it's not what he thought it would be.
Joyce, played by Teri Hatcher.
Ethan Holt, played by James Denton.
Rona, played by Marilu Henner.
Colin, played by Carson Kroeker.
Tisha, played by Sophia Elena Bachart.
Santa, played by John B. Lowe.
Last Christmas is a 2019 Christmas romantic comedy film directed by Paul Feig and written by Bryony
Kimmings and Emma Thompson, who co-developed the story concept with her husband, Greg Wise.
Based on the 1984 song of the same name by Wham!, the film stars Emilia Clarke as a disillusioned Christmas store worker who forms a
relationship with a mysterious man (Henry Golding) and begins to fall for him; Thompson and Michelle Yeoh also star.
Last Christmas was theatrically released in the United States on 8 November 2019
and in the United Kingdom on 15 November 2019 by Universal Pictures.
It received mixed reviews from critics, who praised the performances and chemistry
of Clarke and Golding, but criticised the screenplay and story.
The film grossed $123 million worldwide.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.